annotated-doc==0.0.4
annotated-types==0.7.0
anyio==4.13.0
asttokens==3.0.1
certifi==2026.2.25
cffi==2.0.0
charset-normalizer==3.4.7
click==8.3.2
clickhouse-connect==0.15.1
colorama==0.4.6
comm==0.2.3
contourpy==1.3.3
cryptography==46.0.7
cycler==0.12.1
debugpy==1.8.19
decorator==5.2.1
distro==1.9.0
executing==2.2.1
fastapi==0.136.0
fonttools==4.62.1
google-auth==2.49.2
google-genai==1.73.1
h11==0.16.0
httpcore==1.0.9
httpx==0.28.1
idna==3.11
ipykernel==7.1.0
ipython==9.9.0
ipython_pygments_lexers==1.1.1
jedi==0.19.2
joblib==1.5.3
jupyter_client==8.8.0
jupyter_core==5.9.1
kiwisolver==1.5.0
lz4==4.4.5
matplotlib==3.10.8
matplotlib-inline==0.2.1
nest-asyncio==1.6.0
numpy==2.4.1
packaging==25.0
pandas==3.0.0
parso==0.8.5
pillow==12.2.0
platformdirs==4.5.1
prompt_toolkit==3.0.52
psutil==7.2.1
pure_eval==0.2.3
pyasn1==0.6.3
pyasn1_modules==0.4.2
pycparser==3.0
pydantic==2.13.2
pydantic_core==2.46.2
Pygments==2.19.2
pyparsing==3.3.2
PyQt5==5.15.11
PyQt5-Qt5==5.15.2
PyQt5_sip==12.18.0
python-dateutil==2.9.0.post0
pytz==2026.1.post1
pyzmq==27.1.0
requests==2.33.1
scikit-learn==1.8.0
scipy==1.17.1
six==1.17.0
sniffio==1.3.1
stack-data==0.6.3
starlette==1.0.0
tenacity==9.1.4
threadpoolctl==3.6.0
tornado==6.5.4
traitlets==5.14.3
typing-inspection==0.4.2
typing_extensions==4.15.0
tzdata==2025.3
urllib3==2.6.3
uvicorn==0.44.0
wcwidth==0.2.14
websockets==16.0
xgboost==3.2.0
zstandard==0.25.0
Docker version 29.4.0, build 9d7ad9f
Docker Compose version v5.1.1
Name: fastapi
Version: 0.136.0
Summary: FastAPI framework, high performance, easy to learn, fast to code, ready for production
Home-page: https://github.com/fastapi/fastapi
Author: 
Author-email: =?utf-8?q?Sebasti=C3=A1n_Ram=C3=ADrez?= <tiangolo@gmail.com>
License-Expression: MIT
Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: annotated-doc, pydantic, starlette, typing-extensions, typing-inspection
Required-by: 
---
Name: uvicorn
Version: 0.44.0
Summary: The lightning-fast ASGI server.
Home-page: https://uvicorn.dev/
Author: 
Author-email: Tom Christie <tom@tomchristie.com>
License-Expression: BSD-3-Clause
Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: click, h11
Required-by: 
---
Name: pandas
Version: 3.0.0
Summary: Powerful data structures for data analysis, time series, and statistics
Home-page: https://pandas.pydata.org
Author: 
Author-email: The Pandas Development Team <pandas-dev@python.org>
License: BSD 3-Clause License

 Copyright (c) 2008-2011, AQR Capital Management, LLC, Lambda Foundry, Inc. and PyData Development Team
 All rights reserved.

 Copyright (c) 2011-2026, Open source contributors.

 Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
 modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

 * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this
   list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

 * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
   this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
   and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

 * Neither the name of the copyright holder nor the names of its
   contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
   this software without specific prior written permission.

 THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS"
 AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
 IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
 DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
 FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
 DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
 SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER
 CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
 OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
 OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: numpy, python-dateutil, tzdata
Required-by: 
---
Name: numpy
Version: 2.4.1
Summary: Fundamental package for array computing in Python
Home-page: https://numpy.org
Author: Travis E. Oliphant et al.
Author-email: 
License-Expression: BSD-3-Clause AND 0BSD AND MIT AND Zlib AND CC0-1.0
Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: 
Required-by: contourpy, matplotlib, pandas, scikit-learn, scipy, xgboost
---
Name: scikit-learn
Version: 1.8.0
Summary: A set of python modules for machine learning and data mining
Home-page: https://scikit-learn.org
Author: 
Author-email: 
License-Expression: BSD-3-Clause
Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: joblib, numpy, scipy, threadpoolctl
Required-by: 
---
Name: matplotlib
Version: 3.10.8
Summary: Python plotting package
Home-page: https://matplotlib.org
Author: John D. Hunter, Michael Droettboom
Author-email: Unknown <matplotlib-users@python.org>
License: License agreement for matplotlib versions 1.3.0 and later
 =========================================================

 1. This LICENSE AGREEMENT is between the Matplotlib Development Team
 ("MDT"), and the Individual or Organization ("Licensee") accessing and
 otherwise using matplotlib software in source or binary form and its
 associated documentation.

 2. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License Agreement, MDT
 hereby grants Licensee a nonexclusive, royalty-free, world-wide license
 to reproduce, analyze, test, perform and/or display publicly, prepare
 derivative works, distribute, and otherwise use matplotlib
 alone or in any derivative version, provided, however, that MDT's
 License Agreement and MDT's notice of copyright, i.e., "Copyright (c)
 2012- Matplotlib Development Team; All Rights Reserved" are retained in
 matplotlib  alone or in any derivative version prepared by
 Licensee.

 3. In the event Licensee prepares a derivative work that is based on or
 incorporates matplotlib or any part thereof, and wants to
 make the derivative work available to others as provided herein, then
 Licensee hereby agrees to include in any such work a brief summary of
 the changes made to matplotlib .

 4. MDT is making matplotlib available to Licensee on an "AS
 IS" basis.  MDT MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR
 IMPLIED.  BY WAY OF EXAMPLE, BUT NOT LIMITATION, MDT MAKES NO AND
 DISCLAIMS ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS
 FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR THAT THE USE OF MATPLOTLIB
 WILL NOT INFRINGE ANY THIRD PARTY RIGHTS.

 5. MDT SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO LICENSEE OR ANY OTHER USERS OF MATPLOTLIB
  FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR
 LOSS AS A RESULT OF MODIFYING, DISTRIBUTING, OR OTHERWISE USING
 MATPLOTLIB , OR ANY DERIVATIVE THEREOF, EVEN IF ADVISED OF
 THE POSSIBILITY THEREOF.

 6. This License Agreement will automatically terminate upon a material
 breach of its terms and conditions.

 7. Nothing in this License Agreement shall be deemed to create any
 relationship of agency, partnership, or joint venture between MDT and
 Licensee.  This License Agreement does not grant permission to use MDT
 trademarks or trade name in a trademark sense to endorse or promote
 products or services of Licensee, or any third party.

 8. By copying, installing or otherwise using matplotlib ,
 Licensee agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions of this License
 Agreement.

 License agreement for matplotlib versions prior to 1.3.0
 ========================================================

 1. This LICENSE AGREEMENT is between John D. Hunter ("JDH"), and the
 Individual or Organization ("Licensee") accessing and otherwise using
 matplotlib software in source or binary form and its associated
 documentation.

 2. Subject to the terms and conditions of this License Agreement, JDH
 hereby grants Licensee a nonexclusive, royalty-free, world-wide license
 to reproduce, analyze, test, perform and/or display publicly, prepare
 derivative works, distribute, and otherwise use matplotlib
 alone or in any derivative version, provided, however, that JDH's
 License Agreement and JDH's notice of copyright, i.e., "Copyright (c)
 2002-2011 John D. Hunter; All Rights Reserved" are retained in
 matplotlib  alone or in any derivative version prepared by
 Licensee.

 3. In the event Licensee prepares a derivative work that is based on or
 incorporates matplotlib  or any part thereof, and wants to
 make the derivative work available to others as provided herein, then
 Licensee hereby agrees to include in any such work a brief summary of
 the changes made to matplotlib.

 4. JDH is making matplotlib  available to Licensee on an "AS
 IS" basis.  JDH MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR
 IMPLIED.  BY WAY OF EXAMPLE, BUT NOT LIMITATION, JDH MAKES NO AND
 DISCLAIMS ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS
 FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR THAT THE USE OF MATPLOTLIB
 WILL NOT INFRINGE ANY THIRD PARTY RIGHTS.

 5. JDH SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO LICENSEE OR ANY OTHER USERS OF MATPLOTLIB
  FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR
 LOSS AS A RESULT OF MODIFYING, DISTRIBUTING, OR OTHERWISE USING
 MATPLOTLIB , OR ANY DERIVATIVE THEREOF, EVEN IF ADVISED OF
 THE POSSIBILITY THEREOF.

 6. This License Agreement will automatically terminate upon a material
 breach of its terms and conditions.

 7. Nothing in this License Agreement shall be deemed to create any
 relationship of agency, partnership, or joint venture between JDH and
 Licensee.  This License Agreement does not grant permission to use JDH
 trademarks or trade name in a trademark sense to endorse or promote
 products or services of Licensee, or any third party.

 8. By copying, installing or otherwise using matplotlib,
 Licensee agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions of this License
 Agreement.
 ----

 This binary distrubution of Matplotlib can also bundle the following software
 (depending on the build):

 Name: AMS Fonts
 Files: matplotlib/tests/cmr10.pfb
 Description: Type-1 version of one of Knuth's Computer Modern fonts
 License: OFL-1.1
   The cmr10.pfb file is a Type-1 version of one of Knuth's Computer Modern fonts.
   It is included here as test data only, but the following license applies.

   Copyright (c) 1997, 2009, American Mathematical Society (http://www.ams.org).
   All Rights Reserved.

   "cmb10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbsy10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbsy5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbsy6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbsy7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbsy8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbsy9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbx10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbx12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbx5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbx6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbx7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbx8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbx9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbxsl10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmbxti10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmcsc10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmcsc8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmcsc9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmdunh10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmex10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmex7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmex8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmex9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmff10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmfi10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmfib8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cminch" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmitt10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmi10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmi12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmi5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmi6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmi7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmi8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmi9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmib10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmib5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmib6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmib7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmib8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmmib9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr17" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmr9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsl10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsl12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsl8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsl9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsltt10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmss10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmss12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmss17" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmss8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmss9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssbx10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssdc10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssi10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssi12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssi17" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssi8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssi9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssq8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmssqi8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsy10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsy5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsy6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsy7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsy8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmsy9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtcsc10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtex10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtex8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtex9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmti10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmti12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmti7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmti8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmti9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtt10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtt12" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtt8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmtt9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmu10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "cmvtt10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "euex10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "euex7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "euex8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "euex9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eufb10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eufb5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eufb7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eufm10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eufm5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eufm7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eurb10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eurb5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eurb7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eurm10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eurm5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eurm7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eusb10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eusb5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eusb7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eusm10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eusm5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "eusm7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lasy10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lasy5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lasy6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lasy7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lasy8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lasy9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lasyb10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lcircle1" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lcirclew" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lcmss8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lcmssb8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "lcmssi8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "line10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "linew10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msam10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msam5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msam6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msam7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msam8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msam9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msbm10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msbm5" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msbm6" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msbm7" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msbm8" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "msbm9" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "wncyb10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "wncyi10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "wncyr10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "wncysc10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.
   "wncyss10" is a Reserved Font Name for this Font Software.

   This Font Software is licensed under the SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1.
   This license is copied below, and is also available with a FAQ at:
   http://scripts.sil.org/OFL

   -----------------------------------------------------------
   SIL OPEN FONT LICENSE Version 1.1 - 26 February 2007
   -----------------------------------------------------------

   PREAMBLE
   The goals of the Open Font License (OFL) are to stimulate worldwide
   development of collaborative font projects, to support the font creation
   efforts of academic and linguistic communities, and to provide a free and
   open framework in which fonts may be shared and improved in partnership
   with others.

   The OFL allows the licensed fonts to be used, studied, modified and
   redistributed freely as long as they are not sold by themselves. The
   fonts, including any derivative works, can be bundled, embedded, 
   redistributed and/or sold with any software provided that any reserved
   names are not used by derivative works. The fonts and derivatives,
   however, cannot be released under any other type of license. The
   requirement for fonts to remain under this license does not apply
   to any document created using the fonts or their derivatives.

   DEFINITIONS
   "Font Software" refers to the set of files released by the Copyright
   Holder(s) under this license and clearly marked as such. This may
   include source files, build scripts and documentation.

   "Reserved Font Name" refers to any names specified as such after the
   copyright statement(s).

   "Original Version" refers to the collection of Font Software components as
   distributed by the Copyright Holder(s).

   "Modified Version" refers to any derivative made by adding to, deleting,
   or substituting -- in part or in whole -- any of the components of the
   Original Version, by changing formats or by porting the Font Software to a
   new environment.

   "Author" refers to any designer, engineer, programmer, technical
   writer or other person who contributed to the Font Software.

   PERMISSION & CONDITIONS
   Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
   a copy of the Font Software, to use, study, copy, merge, embed, modify,
   redistribute, and sell modified and unmodified copies of the Font
   Software, subject to the following conditions:

   1) Neither the Font Software nor any of its individual components,
   in Original or Modified Versions, may be sold by itself.

   2) Original or Modified Versions of the Font Software may be bundled,
   redistributed and/or sold with any software, provided that each copy
   contains the above copyright notice and this license. These can be
   included either as stand-alone text files, human-readable headers or
   in the appropriate machine-readable metadata fields within text or
   binary files as long as those fields can be easily viewed by the user.

   3) No Modified Version of the Font Software may use the Reserved Font
   Name(s) unless explicit written permission is granted by the corresponding
   Copyright Holder. This restriction only applies to the primary font name as
   presented to the users.

   4) The name(s) of the Copyright Holder(s) or the Author(s) of the Font
   Software shall not be used to promote, endorse or advertise any
   Modified Version, except to acknowledge the contribution(s) of the
   Copyright Holder(s) and the Author(s) or with their explicit written
   permission.

   5) The Font Software, modified or unmodified, in part or in whole,
   must be distributed entirely under this license, and must not be
   distributed under any other license. The requirement for fonts to
   remain under this license does not apply to any document created
   using the Font Software.

   TERMINATION
   This license becomes null and void if any of the above conditions are
   not met.

   DISCLAIMER
   THE FONT SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
   EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF
   MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT
   OF COPYRIGHT, PATENT, TRADEMARK, OR OTHER RIGHT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
   COPYRIGHT HOLDER BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
   INCLUDING ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
   DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
   FROM, OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE FONT SOFTWARE OR FROM
   OTHER DEALINGS IN THE FONT SOFTWARE.



 Name: BaKoMa Fonts
 Files: matplotlib/mpl-data/fonts/ttf/cm*.ttf matplotlib/mpl-data/fonts/afm/cm*.afm 
 Description: Computer Modern Fonts in PostScript Type 1 and TrueType font formats.
 License: BaKoMa Fonts Licence
         BaKoMa Fonts Licence
         --------------------

     This licence covers two font packs (known as BaKoMa Fonts Collection,
     which is available at `CTAN:fonts/cm/ps-type1/bakoma/'):

       1) BaKoMa-CM (1.1/12-Nov-94)
          Computer Modern Fonts in PostScript Type 1 and TrueType font formats.

       2) BaKoMa-AMS (1.2/19-Jan-95)
          AMS TeX fonts in PostScript Type 1 and TrueType font formats.

     Copyright (C) 1994, 1995, Basil K. Malyshev. All Rights Reserved.

     Permission to copy and distribute these fonts for any purpose is 
     hereby granted without fee, provided that the above copyright notice, 
     author statement and this permission notice appear in all copies of 
     these fonts and related documentation.

     Permission to modify and distribute modified fonts for any purpose is 
     hereby granted without fee, provided that the copyright notice, 
     author statement, this permission notice and location of original 
     fonts (http://www.ctan.org/tex-archive/fonts/cm/ps-type1/bakoma)
     appear in all copies of modified fonts and related documentation.

     Permission to use these fonts (embedding into PostScript, PDF, SVG
     and printing by using any software) is hereby granted without fee. 
     It is not required to provide any notices about using these fonts.

    Basil K. Malyshev
    INSTITUTE FOR HIGH ENERGY PHYSICS
    IHEP, OMVT
    Moscow Region
    142281 PROTVINO
    RUSSIA

    E-Mail:     bakoma@mail.ru
         or     malyshev@mail.ihep.ru




 Name: ColorBrewer Color Schemes
 Files: lib/matplotlib/_cm.py
 Description: Color schemes from ColorBrewer
 License: Apache-2.0
   Apache-Style Software License for ColorBrewer software and ColorBrewer Color Schemes

   Copyright (c) 2002 Cynthia Brewer, Mark Harrower, and The Pennsylvania State University.

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed
   under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR
   CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the
   specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.


 Name: Courier 10
 Files: matplotlib/tests/Courier10PitchBT-Bold.pfb
 Description: Courier 10 font, used in tests.
 License: Bitstream-Charter
   The Courier10PitchBT-Bold.pfb file is a Type-1 version of
   Courier 10 Pitch BT Bold by Bitstream, obtained from
   <https://ctan.org/tex-archive/fonts/courierten>. It is included
   here as test data only, but the following license applies.


   (c) Copyright 1989-1992, Bitstream Inc., Cambridge, MA.

   You are hereby granted permission under all Bitstream propriety rights
   to use, copy, modify, sublicense, sell, and redistribute the 4 Bitstream
   Charter (r) Type 1 outline fonts and the 4 Courier Type 1 outline fonts
   for any purpose and without restriction; provided, that this notice is
   left intact on all copies of such fonts and that Bitstream's trademark
   is acknowledged as shown below on all unmodified copies of the 4 Charter
   Type 1 fonts.

   BITSTREAM CHARTER is a registered trademark of Bitstream Inc.



 Name: JSXTools resize observer
 Files: 
 Description: Minimal polyfill for the ResizeObserver API
 License: CC0-1.0
   # CC0 1.0 Universal

   ## Statement of Purpose

   The laws of most jurisdictions throughout the world automatically confer
   exclusive Copyright and Related Rights (defined below) upon the creator and
   subsequent owner(s) (each and all, an ôownerö) of an original work of
   authorship and/or a database (each, a ôWorkö).

   Certain owners wish to permanently relinquish those rights to a Work for the
   purpose of contributing to a commons of creative, cultural and scientific works
   (ôCommonsö) that the public can reliably and without fear of later claims of
   infringement build upon, modify, incorporate in other works, reuse and
   redistribute as freely as possible in any form whatsoever and for any purposes,
   including without limitation commercial purposes. These owners may contribute
   to the Commons to promote the ideal of a free culture and the further
   production of creative, cultural and scientific works, or to gain reputation or
   greater distribution for their Work in part through the use and efforts of
   others.

   For these and/or other purposes and motivations, and without any expectation of
   additional consideration or compensation, the person associating CC0 with a
   Work (the ôAffirmerö), to the extent that he or she is an owner of Copyright
   and Related Rights in the Work, voluntarily elects to apply CC0 to the Work and
   publicly distribute the Work under its terms, with knowledge of his or her
   Copyright and Related Rights in the Work and the meaning and intended legal
   effect of CC0 on those rights.

   1. Copyright and Related Rights. A Work made available under CC0 may be
      protected by copyright and related or neighboring rights (ôCopyright and
      Related Rightsö). Copyright and Related Rights include, but are not limited
      to, the following:
      1. the right to reproduce, adapt, distribute, perform, display, communicate,
         and translate a Work;
      2. moral rights retained by the original author(s) and/or performer(s);
      3. publicity and privacy rights pertaining to a personÆs image or likeness
         depicted in a Work;
      4. rights protecting against unfair competition in regards to a Work,
         subject to the limitations in paragraph 4(i), below;
      5. rights protecting the extraction, dissemination, use and reuse of data in
         a Work;
      6. database rights (such as those arising under Directive 96/9/EC of the
         European Parliament and of the Council of 11 March 1996 on the legal
         protection of databases, and under any national implementation thereof,
         including any amended or successor version of such directive); and
      7. other similar, equivalent or corresponding rights throughout the world
         based on applicable law or treaty, and any national implementations
         thereof.

   2. Waiver. To the greatest extent permitted by, but not in contravention of,
      applicable law, Affirmer hereby overtly, fully, permanently, irrevocably and
      unconditionally waives, abandons, and surrenders all of AffirmerÆs Copyright
      and Related Rights and associated claims and causes of action, whether now
      known or unknown (including existing as well as future claims and causes of
      action), in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the maximum
      duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time
      extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of
      copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation
      commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the ôWaiverö). Affirmer
      makes the Waiver for the benefit of each member of the public at large and
      to the detriment of AffirmerÆs heirs and successors, fully intending that
      such Waiver shall not be subject to revocation, rescission, cancellation,
      termination, or any other legal or equitable action to disrupt the quiet
      enjoyment of the Work by the public as contemplated by AffirmerÆs express
      Statement of Purpose.

   3. Public License Fallback. Should any part of the Waiver for any reason be
      judged legally invalid or ineffective under applicable law, then the Waiver
      shall be preserved to the maximum extent permitted taking into account
      AffirmerÆs express Statement of Purpose. In addition, to the extent the
      Waiver is so judged Affirmer hereby grants to each affected person a
      royalty-free, non transferable, non sublicensable, non exclusive,
      irrevocable and unconditional license to exercise AffirmerÆs Copyright and
      Related Rights in the Work (i) in all territories worldwide, (ii) for the
      maximum duration provided by applicable law or treaty (including future time
      extensions), (iii) in any current or future medium and for any number of
      copies, and (iv) for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation
      commercial, advertising or promotional purposes (the ôLicenseö). The License
      shall be deemed effective as of the date CC0 was applied by Affirmer to the
      Work. Should any part of the License for any reason be judged legally
      invalid or ineffective under applicable law, such partial invalidity or
      ineffectiveness shall not invalidate the remainder of the License, and in
      such case Affirmer hereby affirms that he or she will not (i) exercise any
      of his or her remaining Copyright and Related Rights in the Work or (ii)
      assert any associated claims and causes of action with respect to the Work,
      in either case contrary to AffirmerÆs express Statement of Purpose.

   4. Limitations and Disclaimers.
      1. No trademark or patent rights held by Affirmer are waived, abandoned,
         surrendered, licensed or otherwise affected by this document.
      2. Affirmer offers the Work as-is and makes no representations or warranties
         of any kind concerning the Work, express, implied, statutory or
         otherwise, including without limitation warranties of title,
         merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non infringement, or
         the absence of latent or other defects, accuracy, or the present or
         absence of errors, whether or not discoverable, all to the greatest
         extent permissible under applicable law.
      3. Affirmer disclaims responsibility for clearing rights of other persons
         that may apply to the Work or any use thereof, including without
         limitation any personÆs Copyright and Related Rights in the Work.
         Further, Affirmer disclaims responsibility for obtaining any necessary
         consents, permissions or other rights required for any use of the Work.
      4. Affirmer understands and acknowledges that Creative Commons is not a
         party to this document and has no duty or obligation with respect to this
         CC0 or use of the Work.

   For more information, please see
   http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/.


 Name: QHull
 Files: matplotlib/_qhull.*.so
 Description: Convex hull, Delaunay triangulation, Voronoi diagrams, Halfspace intersection
 License: Qhull
                       Qhull, Copyright (c) 1993-2020

                               C.B. Barber
                              Arlington, MA 

                                  and

          The National Science and Technology Research Center for
           Computation and Visualization of Geometric Structures
                           (The Geometry Center)
                          University of Minnesota

                          email: qhull@qhull.org

   This software includes Qhull from C.B. Barber and The Geometry Center.  
   Files derived from Qhull 1.0 are copyrighted by the Geometry Center.  The
   remaining files are copyrighted by C.B. Barber.  Qhull is free software 
   and may be obtained via http from www.qhull.org.  It may be freely copied, 
   modified, and redistributed under the following conditions:

   1. All copyright notices must remain intact in all files.

   2. A copy of this text file must be distributed along with any copies 
      of Qhull that you redistribute; this includes copies that you have 
      modified, or copies of programs or other software products that 
      include Qhull.

   3. If you modify Qhull, you must include a notice giving the
      name of the person performing the modification, the date of
      modification, and the reason for such modification.

   4. When distributing modified versions of Qhull, or other software 
      products that include Qhull, you must provide notice that the original 
      source code may be obtained as noted above.

   5. There is no warranty or other guarantee of fitness for Qhull, it is 
      provided solely "as is".  Bug reports or fixes may be sent to 
      qhull_bug@qhull.org; the authors may or may not act on them as 
      they desire.


 Name: Qt4 Editor
 Files: matplotlib/backends/qt_editor
 Description: Module creating PyQt4 form dialogs/layouts to edit various type of parameters
 License: MIT
   Module creating PyQt4 form dialogs/layouts to edit various type of parameters


   formlayout License Agreement (MIT License)
   ------------------------------------------

   Copyright (c) 2009 Pierre Raybaut

   Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person
   obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation
   files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without
   restriction, including without limitation the rights to use,
   copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
   copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the
   Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following
   conditions:

   The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
   included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

   THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
   EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES
   OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
   NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT
   HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
   WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
   FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR
   OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
   """


 Name: Solarized
 Files: matplotlib/mpl-data/stylelib/Solarize_Light2.mplstyle
 Description: Solarized color scheme/style
 License: MIT
   https://github.com/altercation/solarized/blob/master/LICENSE
   Copyright (c) 2011 Ethan Schoonover

   Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
   of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
   in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
   to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
   copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
   furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

   The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
   all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

   THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
   IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
   FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
   AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
   LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
   OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
   THE SOFTWARE.


 Name: Stix fonts
 Files: matplotlib/mpl-data/fonts/ttf/STIX*.ttf
 Description: STIX fonts
 License:
   TERMS AND CONDITIONS

      1. Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person 
   obtaining a copy of the STIX Fonts-TM set accompanying this license 
   (collectively, the "Fonts") and the associated documentation files 
   (collectively with the Fonts, the "Font Software"), to reproduce and 
   distribute the Font Software, including the rights to use, copy, merge 
   and publish copies of the Font Software, and to permit persons to whom 
   the Font Software is furnished to do so same, subject to the following 
   terms and conditions (the "License").

      2. The following copyright and trademark notice and these Terms and 
   Conditions shall be included in all copies of one or more of the Font 
   typefaces and any derivative work created as permitted under this 
   License:

     Copyright (c) 2001-2005 by the STI Pub Companies, consisting of 
   the American Institute of Physics, the American Chemical Society, the 
   American Mathematical Society, the American Physical Society, Elsevier, 
   Inc., and The Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers, Inc. 
   Portions copyright (c) 1998-2003 by MicroPress, Inc. Portions copyright 
   (c) 1990 by Elsevier, Inc. All rights reserved. STIX Fonts-TM is a 
   trademark of The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc.

      3. You may (a) convert the Fonts from one format to another (e.g., 
   from TrueType to PostScript), in which case the normal and reasonable 
   distortion that occurs during such conversion shall be permitted and (b) 
   embed or include a subset of the Fonts in a document for the purposes of 
   allowing users to read text in the document that utilizes the Fonts. In 
   each case, you may use the STIX Fonts-TM mark to designate the resulting 
   Fonts or subset of the Fonts.

      4. You may also (a) add glyphs or characters to the Fonts, or modify 
   the shape of existing glyphs, so long as the base set of glyphs is not 
   removed and (b) delete glyphs or characters from the Fonts, provided 
   that the resulting font set is distributed with the following 
   disclaimer: "This [name] font does not include all the Unicode points 
   covered in the STIX Fonts-TM set but may include others." In each case, 
   the name used to denote the resulting font set shall not include the 
   term "STIX" or any similar term.

      5. You may charge a fee in connection with the distribution of the 
   Font Software, provided that no copy of one or more of the individual 
   Font typefaces that form the STIX Fonts-TM set may be sold by itself.

      6. THE FONT SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY 
   KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES 
   OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT 
   OF COPYRIGHT, PATENT, TRADEMARK OR OTHER RIGHT. IN NO EVENT SHALL 
   MICROPRESS OR ANY OF THE STI PUB COMPANIES BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, 
   DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY GENERAL, 
   SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN 
   ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM OR OUT OF THE USE OR 
   INABILITY TO USE THE FONT SOFTWARE OR FROM OTHER DEALINGS IN THE FONT 
   SOFTWARE.

      7. Except as contained in the notice set forth in Section 2, the 
   names MicroPress Inc. and STI Pub Companies, as well as the names of the 
   companies/organizations that compose the STI Pub Companies, shall not be 
   used in advertising or otherwise to promote the sale, use or other 
   dealings in the Font Software without the prior written consent of the 
   respective company or organization.

      8. This License shall become null and void in the event of any 
   material breach of the Terms and Conditions herein by licensee.

      9. A substantial portion of the STIX Fonts set was developed by 
   MicroPress Inc. for the STI Pub Companies. To obtain additional 
   mathematical fonts, please contact MicroPress, Inc., 68-30 Harrow 
   Street, Forest Hills, NY 11375, USA - Phone: (718) 575-1816.


 Name: Yorick Colormaps
 Files: lib/matplotlib/_cm.py
 Description: Gist/Yorick colormaps
 License:
   BSD-style license for gist/yorick colormaps.

   Copyright:

     Copyright (c) 1996.  The Regents of the University of California.
          All rights reserved.

   Permission to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software for any
   purpose without fee is hereby granted, provided that this entire
   notice is included in all copies of any software which is or includes
   a copy or modification of this software and in all copies of the
   supporting documentation for such software.

   This work was produced at the University of California, Lawrence
   Livermore National Laboratory under contract no. W-7405-ENG-48 between
   the U.S. Department of Energy and The Regents of the University of
   California for the operation of UC LLNL.


               DISCLAIMER

   This software was prepared as an account of work sponsored by an
   agency of the United States Government.  Neither the United States
   Government nor the University of California nor any of their
   employees, makes any warranty, express or implied, or assumes any
   liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or
   usefulness of any information, apparatus, product, or process
   disclosed, or represents that its use would not infringe
   privately-owned rights.  Reference herein to any specific commercial
   products, process, or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer,
   or otherwise, does not necessarily constitute or imply its
   endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by the United States
   Government or the University of California.  The views and opinions of
   authors expressed herein do not necessarily state or reflect those of
   the United States Government or the University of California, and
   shall not be used for advertising or product endorsement purposes.


           AUTHOR

   David H. Munro wrote Yorick and Gist.  Berkeley Yacc (byacc) generated
   the Yorick parser.  The routines in Math are from LAPACK and FFTPACK;
   MathC contains C translations by David H. Munro.  The algorithms for
   Yorick's random number generator and several special functions in
   Yorick/include were taken from Numerical Recipes by Press, et. al.,
   although the Yorick implementations are unrelated to those in
   Numerical Recipes.  A small amount of code in Gist was adapted from
   the X11R4 release, copyright M.I.T. -- the complete copyright notice
   may be found in the (unused) file Gist/host.c.

Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: contourpy, cycler, fonttools, kiwisolver, numpy, packaging, pillow, pyparsing, python-dateutil
Required-by: 
---
Name: joblib
Version: 1.5.3
Summary: Lightweight pipelining with Python functions
Home-page: https://joblib.readthedocs.io
Author: 
Author-email: Gael Varoquaux <gael.varoquaux@normalesup.org>
License-Expression: BSD-3-Clause
Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: 
Required-by: scikit-learn
---
Name: xgboost
Version: 3.2.0
Summary: XGBoost Python Package
Home-page: 
Author: 
Author-email: Hyunsu Cho <chohyu01@cs.washington.edu>, Jiaming Yuan <jm.yuan@outlook.com>
License: Apache-2.0
Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: numpy, scipy
Required-by: 
---
Name: clickhouse-connect
Version: 0.15.1
Summary: ClickHouse Database Core Driver for Python, Pandas, and Superset
Home-page: https://github.com/ClickHouse/clickhouse-connect
Author: ClickHouse Inc.
Author-email: clients@clickhouse.com
License: Apache License 2.0
Location: C:\Users\MGM\AppData\Local\Programs\Python\Python314\Lib\site-packages
Requires: certifi, lz4, pytz, urllib3, zstandard
Required-by: 
